Dmitrii Ivanushkin Software Engineer

Brno, Czech Republic

dmitrii.online github.com/lasjdhu linkedin.com/in/dmitrii-ivanushkin

SUMMARY

Software engineer with 2 years of Frontend experience. Enhanced application performance by 40%, achieved 100% accessibility compliance, and successfully migrated 50K lines to TypeScript while serving 10K+ users. Skilled in React and React Native, delivering cross-platform solutions with 85% test coverage and optimized API communication.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer

Apr 2023 - Present

2023 - Present

Masaryk University

- Enhanced <u>MUNI HELPS</u> application performance by 40%, leveraging Google Lighthouse metrics to optimize user experience for 10K+ users.
- Migrated 50K lines of code from JavaScript to TypeScript within 3 months, improving code reliability and reducing bugs through static typing.
- Maintained cross-platform compatibility for Web, Android, and iOS for two years, enhancing user access and engagement.
- Achieved 100% accessibility compliance within 1 month by collaborating with Theresias Support Centre professionals, ensuring inclusiveness for all users.
- Developed unit and integration tests with Jest and Cypress, achieving 90% code coverage increasing maintainability and reliability of application.

EDUCATION

Information Technology, Bc. Degree	Sep
------------------------------------	-----

Brno University of Technology

International Exchange, Diploma

Apr 2019 - May 2019

Skive College in Denmark

Business IT, High School Diploma Sep 2018 - June 2020

Business High School

CERTIFICATIONS AND COURSES

React: Server-Side Rendering	Nov 2024

LinkedIn

Frontend Developer Professional Certificate Sep 2022

Meta

B2 CEFR Czech Language Certificate May 2021

GoStudy Language School

AWARDS

Hackathon Top 6% Finalist Jan 2024

Major League Hacking

SKILLS

JavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS, Tailwind, Redux, Zustand, React, Next.js, Astro, Three.js, MUI, Expo, React Native, Java, Kotlin, Gluestack UI, Git, Linux, Jest, Cypress, Webpack, Vite, Docker, CI/CD, Jira, English, Czech, Russian